convert2media.com 2010-12-14

# Privacy Policy | Convert 2 Media

### PRIVACY POLICY OF Convert2Media, LLC

Including all Related Websites Owned or Registered to Convert2Media, LLC

Agreement to Access the Site:

Convert2Media, LLC, (“CONVERT2MEDIA”), a Nevada Limited Liability Company is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains the data collection and use practices of CONVERT2MEDIA and all related websites owned or registered to CONVERT2MEDIA. It does not apply to any third party websites, applications, products or services for which CONVERT2MEDIA is not responsible.

By accessing this site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this policy as well as the Acceptable Use Policy and the site’s Publisher Terms and Conditions and Advertiser Terms and Conditions. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, THE ACCEPTABLE USE POLICY OR THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS PROVIDED ON THIS SITE, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO CONVERT2MEDIA OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEBSITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

#### Changes to Privacy Policy:

This Privacy Policy changes from time to time and changes are effective upon posting. It is your sole responsibility to periodically review this policy for updates and you are solely responsible to be aware of any changes to this and all posted policies on this website. CONVERT2MEDIA does not provide notices of any changes in any manner other than by posting the changes at this website.

#### Information Collection, Use, and Dissemination practices:

This policy applies to CONVERT2MEDIA's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by CONVERT2MEDIA on its, (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Websites"), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to CONVERT2MEDIA's other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties, or the use of customer lists from third parties. CONVERT2MEDIA is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party websites or applications.

1\. Collection of Information.

1.1. User Direct Information:

Each time you provide information to take advantage of a promotional offer, enter to win a contest, enter to win a sweepstake, send us an email, or otherwise transmit information via the site, CONVERT2MEDIA may obtain and collect personally identifiable information provided by you, including, but not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, social security number, credit card information, and telephone number. You may also provide us with information that, when combined with personally identifiable information, provides us with a better idea of who you are, including but not limited to your gender, birthday, marital status, and education level (collectively referred to as "personal information"). If you choose to access our website, use our services or purchase our products, we may require you to provide personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the site.

1.2. Survey Information:

CONVERT2MEDIA collects information from you when you voluntarily complete a CONVERT2MEDIA survey, order form, or a registration page either online by using the internet, offline by providing this information through the mail, in person or using a telephone. This information may be collected by surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties. This method of collection is collectively known as a “Survey.” In such Surveys, CONVERT2MEDIA or a third party may ask you to provide personal identifiable information including your name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time. CONVERT2MEDIA may also collect such information concerning you from another source and uses that information in combination with information provided from this website. Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and you are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to CONVERT2MEDIA or a third party, but you may receive incentives from CONVERT2MEDIA or a third party in exchange for providing such information.

1.3. Third Party List Information:

CONVERT2MEDIA may collect information from you when you provide information to a third party and CONVERT2MEDIA subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the third party. Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the third party. When acquiring this information, CONVERT2MEDIA seeks assurances from the third party that it has a right to transfer the information to CONVERT2MEDIA and that the third party has a right to provide offers from advertisers to you included on the third party list.

1.4. Other Methods of Collecting Personal Information:

Other occasions when CONVERT2MEDIA obtains information from you include (1) your claiming a prize or seeking to redeem an incentive offered by CONVERT2MEDIA or by a third party, (2) your requests for assistance through CONVERT2MEDIA's customer service department, and (3) when you voluntarily subscribe to a CONVERT2MEDIA service or newsletter.

1.5. Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology:

CONVERT2MEDIA currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you with information about you in its database. Additionally, CONVERT2MEDIA may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future. (a) Cookies: “Cookies” are a feature on your browser software. If enabled, we may write cookies that may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of the pages of this Site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features appeal the most to you and what content you may have viewed on past visits. When you visit this site again, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. We may use cookies to: keep track of the number of return visits to this site; accumulate and report aggregate, statistical information on website usage; deliver specific content to you based on your interests or past viewing history; save your password for ease of access to our Site. You can disable cookies, although the Site may not function properly for you. Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set. You may read more about cookies at [http://cookiecentral.com](http://cookiecentral.com/ "http://cookiecentral.com"). In order to use all of the features and functionality of CONVERT2MEDIA’s websites, you need to accept cookies. (b) Web Beacons: A web beacon is a programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page, but can also be used to transfer your unique user identification to a database and associate you with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows CONVERT2MEDIA to track certain websites you visit. Web beacons are used to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes to determine products or services you may be interested in. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, CONVERT2MEDIA also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in CONVERT2MEDIA's database. (c) IP Addresses: CONVERT2MEDIA automatically tracks certain information based upon your behavior on the site. We may use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages. (d) Computer Profiles: CONVERT2MEDIA may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data which will help us understand and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors. For instance, CONVERT2MEDIA may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. When you provide us with Personal Identification Information, we are able to use such visitor data to identify you. (e) Data Mining: Data Mining technology may be employed from time to time if used by a Client of CONVERT2MEDIA. (f) New Technology: The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly developing. As a result, CONVERT2MEDIA strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of new technology.

1.6. No Information Collected from Children:

CONVERT2MEDIA will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 18. If CONVERT2MEDIA obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 18, that information will be immediately deleted from its database. Because it does not collect such information, CONVERT2MEDIA has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. CONVERT2MEDIA has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

1.7. Credit Card Information:

CONVERT2MEDIA may, in certain instances, collect credit card numbers and related information when an individual places an order from CONVERT2MEDIA. When the credit card information is submitted to CONVERT2MEDIA, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. CONVERT2MEDIA will use the credit card information for purposes of processing and completing the purchase transaction, and the credit card information will be disclosed to third parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction.

2\. Use of Individual Information.

The following section describes how CONVERT2MEDIA uses personal information. The uses described in these sections may change at any time. CONVERT2MEDIA may also broaden its use of your personal information. CONVERT2MEDIA may also use your personal information to provide commercial promotional offers to individuals or entities through, among other things, email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, banner advertising and package stuffers.

2.1. Discretion to Use Information:

The personal information collected on this site and by third parties will be used to operate the site and to provide the services or products or carry out the transactions you have requested or authorized. CONVERT2MEDIA may change or broaden its use of your personal information at any time. CONVERT2MEDIA may use your personal information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, and other possible uses. CONVERT2MEDIA MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION

2.2. Email:

CONVERT2MEDIA uses your personal information to provide promotional offers by email to you. CONVERT2MEDIA may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If you wish to end your email subscription from a particular list, you only need to press the unsubscribe button on the mail message. To unsubscribe from all CONVERT2MEDIA’s email lists, you must submit your email address at [http://www.Convert2Media.com/unsub.html](http://www.convert2media.com/unsub.html "http://www.Convert2Media.com/unsub.html"). Such an unsubscribe request will permanently delete your email from all lists used by CONVERT2MEDIA. Because CONVERT2MEDIA only sends emails when you have agreed to receive emails from CONVERT2MEDIA or you have agreed to receive emails from third parties, statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to email messages sent by CONVERT2MEDIA. Email messages sent by CONVERT2MEDIA, will contain an advertiser's name in the "From:" line but hitting the "Reply" button will cause a reply email to be sent to CONVERT2MEDIA. The "Subject:" line of a CONVERT2MEDIA email messages will usually contain a line provided from the advertiser to CONVERT2MEDIA.

2.3. Profiling and Target Advertising:

CONVERT2MEDIA uses your information to make and improve profiles of you and to track your online browsing habits and determine which areas of CONVERT2MEDIA's websites are most frequently visited. This information helps CONVERT2MEDIA to better understand your interests so that it can target advertising and promotions to you. CONVERT2MEDIA may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers.

2.4. Storage of Personal Information:

CONVERT2MEDIA stores your information in a database on CONVERT2MEDIA’s servers. Our servers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under CONVERT2MEDIA's control. Notwithstanding such measures, CONVERT2MEDIA cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent CONVERT2MEDIA computers from being illegally accessed, and your information from being stolen or altered.

3\. Use of Personal Information.

3.1. Sale or Transfer to Third Parties:

CONVERT2MEDIA MAY SELL OR TRANSFER YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY PURPOSE IN CONVERT2MEDIA'S SOLE DISCRETION. CONVERT2MEDIA uses your personal information in the following 3 ways: Customer Service; Marketing; and Complying with the law.

3.2. Customer Service:

CONVERT2MEDIA will use your personal information to respond to you, to process, validate and verify requests and/or purchase orders, to fulfill any of your requests and to tailor your experience on our websites.

3.3. Marketing:

CONVERT2MEDIA will use your personal information for any marketing and survey purpose on behalf of CONVERT2MEDIA and its affiliates and subsidiaries to send information to you about additional goods or services that may be of interest to you. In addition, CONVERT2MEDIA will disclose your personal information to third party agents and independent contractors to help us conduct our marketing and survey efforts and to share with other companies in connection with marketing efforts including but not limited to direct marketing. You may have no relationship with these other companies.

3.4. Complying with Legal Process:

CONVERT2MEDIA will use or disclose your personal information in response to subpoenas, court orders, warrants, or legal process, or to otherwise establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or in the event you violate or breach an agreement with CONVERT2MEDIA. CONVERT2MEDIA will use and disclose your personal information if we believe you will harm the property or rights of CONVERT2MEDIA, its owners, or those of CONVERT2MEDIA's other customers. Finally, we will use or disclose your personal information if we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of CONVERT2MEDIA’s acceptable use policy, or as otherwise required by law when responding to subpoenas, court orders and other legal processes.

3.5. Order Fulfillment:

CONVERT2MEDIA will transfer your personal information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that you order from such third party while using CONVERT2MEDIA’s websites or when responding to offers provided by CONVERT2MEDIA.

3.6. Data Summary:

CONVERT2MEDIA may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

3.7. Other Access to Personal Information:

You have access to your personal information collected. You may correct, amend, or delete such information. You may do this by contacting 

This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it

CONVERT2MEDIA may also give advertising clients and email services providers’ access to your email address to verify the origin of the personal information collected.

4\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties.

4.1. Advertiser cookies and web beacons:

Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on the websites and on the internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. CONVERT2MEDIA does not control the use of such technology and CONVERT2MEDIA has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you.

4.2. Links:

The websites and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of third parties. CONVERT2MEDIA is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by third parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. CONVERT2MEDIA does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such third party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

5\. Unsubscribe Procedures.

If you wish to discontinue receiving email messages from CONVERT2MEDIA, you may:

(a) Unsubscribe from one email list. To unsubscribe from a particular list, either (1) submit your email address at [http://www.Convert2Media.com/unsub.html](http://www.convert2media.com/unsub.html "http://www.Convert2Media.com/unsub.html") or (2) follow the instructions in each promotional email message sent by CONVERT2MEDIA.

(b) Unsubscribe from all of Convert2Media email lists.

You may submit your email address at [http://www.Convert2Media.com/unsub.html](http://www.convert2media.com/unsub.html "http://www.Convert2Media.com/unsub.html") or write us at:

**Convert2Media**  
2910 Maguire Road, Suite 2010  
Ocoee, FL 34761

For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).
